<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quiz" >
        <item>if you find a defect while you are testing the software early in the lifecycle, what will be
                impacted by this action?
                A. Risk of finding this defect in operation will increase
                B. Risk of finding this defect in operation will not be impacted
                C. Risk of finding this defect in operation will be reduced </item>

        <item>  What is the main role of the tester in software projects?
                A. resolve defects
                B. develop applications
                C. find defects</item>

        <item>Software testing is a way to …
                A. Increase the quality of the software
                B. Reduce the risk of software failure in operation
                </item>

        <item> Which of the following can be considered as a main objective of software testing?
                A. Market our product to potential customers
                B. Give the client good knowledge about the status of the project
                C. Evaluate other team members and make a decision about their eligibility to get a bonus</item>

        <item>if the tester reviewed the requirements and found a contradiction between two
                requirements, which objective of testing can be obtained using this activity?
                A. Building confidence
                B. Compliance with laws
                C. Preventing defects </item>

        <item> if you are making sure that what you have built is the same as what the client wants,
                which test objective is mostly met by this activity?
                A. Reducing Risks
                B. Finding Defects s
                C. Requirements Fulfilment</item>

        <item> In which lifecycle may testers be involved in debugging and component testing?
                A. Waterfall Model
                B. Agile Development
                C. V-Model </item>

        <item> What is the definition of debugging?
                A. Checking that no unintended consequence have occurred as a result of a fix
                B. Testing/checking whether the software performs correctly
                C. Identifying the cause of a defect, repairing the code and checking the fix is correct
                D. Checking that a previously reported defect has been corrected</item>

        <item>Which of the following is an example of a defect that causes harm?
                A. A usability defect that results in user dissatisfaction
                B. A defect that causes slow response time when running reports
                C. A defect that causes raw sewage to be dumped into the ocean
                D. A regression defect that causes the desktop window to display in green </item>

        <item>Which of the following can be considered as a testing contribution to success?
                A. Reviewing the scope and cost of the project with stakeholders
                B. Reviewing the effort done by the developer in the team and giving some advice to him
                C. Review the design, requirements and code and tracking defects that occurred and that
                need to be solved </item>

        <item> Which of the following is the correct statement?
                A. An error causes a failure which results in a defect
                B. A defect causes a failure which results in an error
                C. A failure is observed as an error and the root cause is the defect
                D. An error causes a defect which is observed as a failure</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>